<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>📖 Introduction</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/introduction/</guid><description>WAHA - WhatsApp HTTP API that you can install on your own server and run in less than 5 minutes!
Get started #
👉 Run WhatsApp API in less than 5 minutes! We will guide you through the necessary steps to successfully send your first text message using WhatsApp API in Quick Start →.
Disclaimer #
This project is not affiliated, associated, authorized, endorsed by, or in any way officially connected with WhatsApp or any of its subsidiaries or its affiliates.</description></item><item><title>⚡ Quick Start</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/quick-start/</guid><description>Step-by-Step guide #
On this page you&amp;rsquo;re going to install and run WAHA, authenticate the client using QR code, and send your first message to WhatsApp using API!
We will guide you through the necessary steps to successfully send your first text message using WhatsApp API.
Are you a visual learner? We&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! Watch the video tutorial below to see how to send your first message using WAHA</description></item><item><title>⚠️ How to Avoid Blocking</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/how-to-avoid-blocking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/how-to-avoid-blocking/</guid><description>How to Avoid Blocking in WhatsApp when developing bots.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to keep in mind that WhatsApp has strict policies in place to prevent spamming and abuse of their platform.
If you&amp;rsquo;re developing a bot for WhatsApp, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to follow these guidelines to avoid getting blocked.
Guidelines to Follow #
1. Only Reply to Messages #
When developing a bot for WhatsApp, you should never initiate a conversation. Instead, your bot should only reply to messages that it receives.</description></item><item><title>❓ FAQ</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/faq/</guid><description>System Requirements #
We strongly recommend using VPS or servers with minimum 2CPU and 2GB RAM configuration for the project even for a single session. If you want to host more sessions - please check the numbers below
How much CPU and Memory does WAHA consume? #
WAHA uses multiple 🏭 Engines under the hood and depends on the used engine CPU and Memory requirements change
WEBJS #
The nature of WEBJS engine - it runs real WhatsApp Web version in Chromium (or Chrome) and communicate with it to prevent blocking from WhatsApp.</description></item><item><title>🔄 Changelog</title><link>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/changelog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://waha.devlike.pro/docs/overview/changelog/</guid><description>If you wish to get and read Release Notes - read them on one of our platforms, these posts are FREE.
Boosty -&amp;gt; Patreon -&amp;gt; dev.to Subscribe for FREE to get new updates there!
💡 Check the 🔧 Install &amp;amp; Update page to learn how to update WAHA.
2024.7 #
2024.7.6 - WEBJS restart fix #444 2024.7.5 - 📰 WhatsApp Channels 2024.7.4 - NOWEB fix profile picture #422 2024.7.3 - added JSON logging format.</description></item></channel></rss>